<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Laser on Annie Sullivan</title>
    <link>/categories/laser/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Laser on Annie Sullivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/laser/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Metal Etching with the Glowforge</title>
      <link>/2019/02/metal-etching-with-glowforge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/02/metal-etching-with-glowforge/</guid>
      <description>One thing I&amp;rsquo;d been really excited to try on my Glowforge was etching metal. Of course the Glowforge doesn&amp;rsquo;t etch metal directly, but there are a lot of posts on the Glowforge forums where people had spray painted metal and then etched it. I was really curious if it was easier to do than the laser transferred resists I&amp;rsquo;d been using. So I searched the forums for all the information I could find on methods people were using, and gave it a shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleach Shirts on the Glowforge</title>
      <link>/2018/12/bleach-shirts-on-the-glowforge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/bleach-shirts-on-the-glowforge/</guid>
      <description>I’ve made a bunch of bleach shirts using stencil vinyl/contact paper on my cricut. But I really wanted to try it on my Glowforge, since it can cut higher detail stencils. I also wanted to try switching to freezer paper, so that I can iron/heat gun the bleached areas of the shirt to make them lighter.
The big problem I had with freezer paper (on both the cricut and the Glowforge) is that it curls up a ton, and I didn’t have a good way to transfer the stencil to the shirt, especially stencils with multiple tiny bits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unglazed bisque ornaments: a happy accident</title>
      <link>/2018/12/unglazed-bisque-ornaments-a-happy-accident/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/unglazed-bisque-ornaments-a-happy-accident/</guid>
      <description>I was really excited about the results I got lasering on porcelain ornaments, so I tried to order a bunch on Amazon Prime. But I didn’t pay close attention to the description and accidentally bought these unfinished bisque ornaments instead. I had been planning to send them back, but I couldn’t stop thinking about what it might look like to try to do a 3d engrave on one. So I picked a test ornament to sacrifice, and tried out a simple gradient with increasing power settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Middle Earth Field Notes Cover</title>
      <link>/2018/08/middle-earth-leather-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/middle-earth-leather-journal/</guid>
      <description>I saw these beautiful map journals and thought it would be fun to make one with a fictional map. Doug’s birthday was coming up and he loves Lord of the Rings, so I decided to try making a Field Notes cover that’s a map of middle earth. I started with the template I used for the Marauder’s Map Field Notes Cover. While I was making the Calvin and Hobbes journal, I made some other journal templates, including a Field Notes cover with pen loop:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calvin  Hobbes Moleskine Cover</title>
      <link>/2018/08/calvin-hobbes-moleskine-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/calvin-hobbes-moleskine-cover/</guid>
      <description>I had a lot of fun making the Marauder’s Map Fields Notes Cover, and I wanted to try something just a little bit more complex. Plus I needed a cover for a bigger journal. So I decided to extend the field notes cover in Illustrator to fit a 5″x8.25″ Moleskine Cahier Journal, and add a pen loop and snap.
Here’s a link to my design, in case anyone wants to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leather field notes cover</title>
      <link>/2018/08/leather-field-notes-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/leather-field-notes-cover/</guid>
      <description>I really wanted to learn more about working with leather after making the Marauder’s Map bookmarks. So when I saw this field notes template on instructables I decided to extend the same design to a Field Notes cover.
I knew I wanted to dye the leather, and I’d need to be able to stitch together pieces, but I had no idea where to start beyond that. I’d heard great things about the customer service at Tandy Leather, so I headed down to the store with a ton of questions, and picked up some 2-3oz veg-tan leather,gel antique, waxed thread, stitching needles, and edge kote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Glowforge Project: Harry Potter Bookmarks</title>
      <link>/2018/07/first-glowforge-project-harry-potter-bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/first-glowforge-project-harry-potter-bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>I just got a Glowforge and I’m so excited! I haven’t had time to make much yet, but it came with a sample of leather, and I thought it would be fun to do Harry Potter bookmarks. So I found an image of the Marauder’s Map online, and quickly threw together the “I solemnly swear..” quote with footprints in Illustrator. I saved them as .png images and uploaded into the Glowforge app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Etched Glass Ornaments</title>
      <link>/2013/12/laser-etched-glass-ornaments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/12/laser-etched-glass-ornaments/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been having a lot of trouble getting photos to look good on ornaments, so I decided to try something else. I had a really cute set of Logan’s footprints from the hospital, and I scanned it in. I wanted to figure out the best way to convert the image to a black and white bitmap, so I could experiment to see which method would etch best on glass. I tried a few different methods:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Etched Corian Marvel Coasters</title>
      <link>/2013/10/laser-etched-corian-coasters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/10/laser-etched-corian-coasters/</guid>
      <description>At one point, we were considering remodeling our kitchen, and we got some Corian samples. We didn’t end up doing the remodel, but we left them sitting around the house to see how durable they are. My brother-in-law had always thought they made cool coasters.
When I took the laser class at Maker Works, I noticed one of the materials that can be etched is Corian. Since my brother-in-law loves superheroes, I thought superhero coasters would be a cool Christmas present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Using the Laser: Etched Wood Photo Ornaments</title>
      <link>/2013/10/first-time-using-the-laser/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/10/first-time-using-the-laser/</guid>
      <description>I got really excited after taking the laser class at Maker Works and decided to try a simple project to start. I didn’t want to worry about dithering photos, so I ran a batch job on all our family photos, putting them through Vector Magic to see which ones converted to single-color vectors the best.
I picked a few of the best ones, added some text in illustrator, and made cut lines for ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>