<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christmas on Annie Sullivan</title>
    <link>/categories/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christmas on Annie Sullivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Baking Gingerbread Houses!</title>
      <link>/2017/12/gingerbread-houses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/gingerbread-houses/</guid>
      <description>As kids we always made milk carton gingerbread houses, but I’ve always wanted to try making a real one. I found this set of gingerbread house cookie cutters with a recipe book at Cost Plus World Market and decided to give it a shot with the kids and their cousin. It took some planning because we needed to bake the dough ahead of time, but overall it was well worth it–the gingerbread pieces held up and stuck together really well, and the kids loved decorating them so much!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knitting Weasley Sweaters</title>
      <link>/2016/11/weasley-sweaters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/11/weasley-sweaters/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been doing a lot of knitting lately, and also a lot of reading Harry Potter to the boys. Logan especially loves it. I finally learned to knit a bottom up sweater, and got some beautiful chunky yarn at Spun, so knitting the boys Weasley sweaters felt like the perfect winter project. I had a lot of fun with it, and will definitely be doing more bottom up sweaters in the future!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Using the Laser: Etched Wood Photo Ornaments</title>
      <link>/2013/10/first-time-using-the-laser/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/10/first-time-using-the-laser/</guid>
      <description>I got really excited after taking the laser class at Maker Works and decided to try a simple project to start. I didn’t want to worry about dithering photos, so I ran a batch job on all our family photos, putting them through Vector Magic to see which ones converted to single-color vectors the best.
I picked a few of the best ones, added some text in illustrator, and made cut lines for ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Printed Metal Christmas Ornaments: Biodh Duil</title>
      <link>/2012/12/biodh-duil-ornaments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/12/biodh-duil-ornaments/</guid>
      <description>My uncle Dick passed away this year, and it was a very sad time for our family because he was such an amazing person and we will all miss him so much. For Christmas, I wanted to do something to remember him. He always loved gadgets and new technology, so I decided to design gifts in Tinkercad and have them 3D printed for the family.
When our family was going through some hard times, Uncle Dick and his daughter Colleen got together and designed a family logo, a tree with a heart and the words “Biodh Duil” (Irish imperative form of the verb “hope”) written below it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitten Christmas Tree Skirt Made with Silhouette Cameo</title>
      <link>/2012/11/christmas-tree-skirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/11/christmas-tree-skirt/</guid>
      <description>I just got a Silhouette Cameo and I am really excited to use it! It can cut paper, cardstock, fabric, vinyl, stickers, and even temporary tattoos into whatever shapes you can put into vector graphic format on your computer. After a few experiments with cardstock, I wanted to make something real. I decided to start small, with a Christmas tree skirt.
I had seen some photos of a tree skirt with mittens on it, and since we live in the mitten state now I thought it would be fun do do something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>