<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2018s on Annie Sullivan</title>
    <link>/2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2018s on Annie Sullivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleach Shirts on the Glowforge</title>
      <link>/2018/12/bleach-shirts-on-the-glowforge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/bleach-shirts-on-the-glowforge/</guid>
      <description>I’ve made a bunch of bleach shirts using stencil vinyl/contact paper on my cricut. But I really wanted to try it on my Glowforge, since it can cut higher detail stencils. I also wanted to try switching to freezer paper, so that I can iron/heat gun the bleached areas of the shirt to make them lighter.
The big problem I had with freezer paper (on both the cricut and the Glowforge) is that it curls up a ton, and I didn’t have a good way to transfer the stencil to the shirt, especially stencils with multiple tiny bits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unglazed bisque ornaments: a happy accident</title>
      <link>/2018/12/unglazed-bisque-ornaments-a-happy-accident/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/unglazed-bisque-ornaments-a-happy-accident/</guid>
      <description>I was really excited about the results I got lasering on porcelain ornaments, so I tried to order a bunch on Amazon Prime. But I didn’t pay close attention to the description and accidentally bought these unfinished bisque ornaments instead. I had been planning to send them back, but I couldn’t stop thinking about what it might look like to try to do a 3d engrave on one. So I picked a test ornament to sacrifice, and tried out a simple gradient with increasing power settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleach Shirts with Polyester Blends</title>
      <link>/2018/11/bleach-shirts-with-polyester-blends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/11/bleach-shirts-with-polyester-blends/</guid>
      <description>All the tutorials for making bleach shirts say to use 100% cotton. But I had some Old Navy 60% cotton 40% polyester blend shirts sitting around, and the kids need some long sleeve shirts for winter. They’ve been asking about deathly hallows shirts after seeing someone wearing one, so I decided to give it a shot.
I made stencils using contact paper on the Cricut. One problem I’ve had is that it’s super easy to make stencils with vinyl or contact paper, but then you can’t iron to lighten the bleach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2018, Part 2: Captain America Costume</title>
      <link>/2018/10/halloween-2018-part-2-captain-america-costume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/halloween-2018-part-2-captain-america-costume/</guid>
      <description>Logan absolutely fell in love with Captain America over the summer, so it was the clear choice for his Halloween costume. I was really excited about this costume. From cute toddler costumes to amazing cosplay constructions, there are tons of great ideas and tutorials online.
Doug and I were both really interested in all the stuff we’ve seen online made out of EVA foam coated in PlastiDip. The shield was the obvious place to try it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2018, Part 1: Lion Costume</title>
      <link>/2018/10/halloween-2018-part-1-lion-costume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/halloween-2018-part-1-lion-costume/</guid>
      <description>Cole loves animals, but his brother convinced him he needed to be something scary for Halloween. After some deep thinking he settled upon a lion, which he decided is scary enough. I took him to Jo Ann to pick out fabric. He settled on a light brown fleece for the fur, and a darker brown fur for the mane.
I also looked at the lion costume patterns, but they were really complicated!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Middle Earth Field Notes Cover</title>
      <link>/2018/08/middle-earth-leather-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/middle-earth-leather-journal/</guid>
      <description>I saw these beautiful map journals and thought it would be fun to make one with a fictional map. Doug’s birthday was coming up and he loves Lord of the Rings, so I decided to try making a Field Notes cover that’s a map of middle earth. I started with the template I used for the Marauder’s Map Field Notes Cover. While I was making the Calvin and Hobbes journal, I made some other journal templates, including a Field Notes cover with pen loop:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calvin  Hobbes Moleskine Cover</title>
      <link>/2018/08/calvin-hobbes-moleskine-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/calvin-hobbes-moleskine-cover/</guid>
      <description>I had a lot of fun making the Marauder’s Map Fields Notes Cover, and I wanted to try something just a little bit more complex. Plus I needed a cover for a bigger journal. So I decided to extend the field notes cover in Illustrator to fit a 5″x8.25″ Moleskine Cahier Journal, and add a pen loop and snap.
Here’s a link to my design, in case anyone wants to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leather field notes cover</title>
      <link>/2018/08/leather-field-notes-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/leather-field-notes-cover/</guid>
      <description>I really wanted to learn more about working with leather after making the Marauder’s Map bookmarks. So when I saw this field notes template on instructables I decided to extend the same design to a Field Notes cover.
I knew I wanted to dye the leather, and I’d need to be able to stitch together pieces, but I had no idea where to start beyond that. I’d heard great things about the customer service at Tandy Leather, so I headed down to the store with a ton of questions, and picked up some 2-3oz veg-tan leather,gel antique, waxed thread, stitching needles, and edge kote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Glowforge Project: Harry Potter Bookmarks</title>
      <link>/2018/07/first-glowforge-project-harry-potter-bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/first-glowforge-project-harry-potter-bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>I just got a Glowforge and I’m so excited! I haven’t had time to make much yet, but it came with a sample of leather, and I thought it would be fun to do Harry Potter bookmarks. So I found an image of the Marauder’s Map online, and quickly threw together the “I solemnly swear..” quote with footprints in Illustrator. I saved them as .png images and uploaded into the Glowforge app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making bleach shirts with stencils cut on Cricut Maker</title>
      <link>/2018/06/bleach-shirts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/bleach-shirts/</guid>
      <description>The Basics I randomly happened upon this subreddit full of bleach shirt pictures and was totally mesmerized. So many different possibilities, and such a simple process. So I started reading up. There are a lot of variations in the process, but making bleach shirts mostly looks like this:
 Use a 100% cotton shirt. Wash the shirt. Lots of shirts come with chemicals on them that will stop the bleach from working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porcelain Pen Ceramic Mug</title>
      <link>/2018/05/decorating-mugs-with-porcelain-pen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/decorating-mugs-with-porcelain-pen/</guid>
      <description>Even after twenty years as a woman in tech, this article about One Direction fans and especially the Larries brought a fresh perspective. I mentioned it to my sister, and as usual, she was way ahead of me. She also loves coffee, so when I found out about porcelain pens, I thought it would be cool to try and make her a Larry Stylinson mug.
I did a Google image search for a good picture and decided to start with this one:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandblasting Pint Glasses and Stemless Wine Glasses</title>
      <link>/2018/04/sandblasting-glass/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/sandblasting-glass/</guid>
      <description>We have been running out of glasses lately and I’ve been thinking about decorating my own. I’ve seen some cool pictures of frosted glass online and wanted to try something like that myself. The first thing I tried was etching cream, which is pretty cheap and easy to find, but I ran into some big problems.
  You can see where the etching cream leaked at the top of the glass, and where it dripped around the back.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>