<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Halloween on Annie Sullivan</title>
    <link>/categories/halloween/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Halloween on Annie Sullivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/halloween/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2019: Knight and Dragon</title>
      <link>/2019/10/halloween-2019-knight-and-dragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/10/halloween-2019-knight-and-dragon/</guid>
      <description>After coming back from a trip to Florida, the kids were excited about the astonaut and knight costumes they saw at Disney and NASA. I pointed Doug to some online tutorials for craft foam helmets. He got really excited about the idea and put some together. They came out great!
  The kids trying on their astronaut and knight helmets.
  Now that Doug had the basic idea from the tutorials, he kept going&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2018, Part 2: Captain America Costume</title>
      <link>/2018/10/halloween-2018-part-2-captain-america-costume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/halloween-2018-part-2-captain-america-costume/</guid>
      <description>Logan absolutely fell in love with Captain America over the summer, so it was the clear choice for his Halloween costume. I was really excited about this costume. From cute toddler costumes to amazing cosplay constructions, there are tons of great ideas and tutorials online.
Doug and I were both really interested in all the stuff we’ve seen online made out of EVA foam coated in PlastiDip. The shield was the obvious place to try it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2018, Part 1: Lion Costume</title>
      <link>/2018/10/halloween-2018-part-1-lion-costume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/halloween-2018-part-1-lion-costume/</guid>
      <description>Cole loves animals, but his brother convinced him he needed to be something scary for Halloween. After some deep thinking he settled upon a lion, which he decided is scary enough. I took him to Jo Ann to pick out fabric. He settled on a light brown fleece for the fur, and a darker brown fur for the mane.
I also looked at the lion costume patterns, but they were really complicated!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2017: Sewing Ghost and Bunny Costumes</title>
      <link>/2017/10/halloween-2017-ghost-and-bunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/halloween-2017-ghost-and-bunny/</guid>
      <description>The kids are really excited about their Halloween costumes this year, and they’ve been in deep debate about what they should be. Logan is adamant that Halloween costumes should be scary, and he wants to be a ghost with glowing red eyes. Cole ignored Logan’s passionate arguments for scary costumes and waffled between pumpkin and bunny for several days, finally deciding to be a bunny.
The bunny was pretty straightforward; I picked up fuzzy bunny fabric at Joann’s and once again used the trusty Running With Scissors woodland animal pattern.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2016: Ninjago!</title>
      <link>/2016/10/halloween-2016-ninjago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/halloween-2016-ninjago/</guid>
      <description>My dad passed away this week. It’s an especially sad time of year because he always made such amazing Halloween costumes for us as kids. He and my mom would work as a team–she did a lot of research, finding sewing patterns and techniques in magazines, and he did a ton of awesome engineering work bringing chicken wire and masking tape and foam and spray paint together into these amazing works of art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2015: Mike Wazowski Toddler Costume</title>
      <link>/2015/10/halloween-2015-monsters-inc-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/10/halloween-2015-monsters-inc-update/</guid>
      <description>This year, Logan loves his old costume and it still fit, but Cole is big enough to walk around! So I updated his Mike Wazowski costume, again with a green fleece bodysuit based on the trusty old Running With Scissors pattern, and taking Mike’s face off our baby carrier and putting it on an over-the-shoulder sack fleece cutout, which we stuffed with a pillow.
  
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2014: Monsters Inc Sully and Mike Wazowski!</title>
      <link>/2014/10/halloween-2014-monsters-inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/10/halloween-2014-monsters-inc/</guid>
      <description>This is our first Halloween with two kids and I was excited to work on costumes for both of them. Logan loved watching Monsters Inc so I decided to do Sully and Mike Wazowski costumes.
I started work on Logan’s Sully costume first. After much Googling, I decided to buy a vintage McCall’s 6628 pattern online, and I bought turquoise fur fabric at fabric.com. After those arrived, there was a lot of cutting and sewing to do!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2013: Sewing a Curious George Costume</title>
      <link>/2013/10/halloween-2013-curious-george/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/10/halloween-2013-curious-george/</guid>
      <description>This Halloween, Logan was obsessed with Curious George. So it was easy to pick out a costume idea for him. I picked up some brown fleece and sewed up the same Running With Scissors pattern I used last year. Here’s a pic of Logan trying it on (sorry for the blurriness, he’s pretty hard to catch standing still!)
  Jumping on the bed wearing the costume base. Could only get a blurry picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logan&#39;s First Halloween Costume: Max&#39;s Wolfsuit from Where the Wild Things Are</title>
      <link>/2012/11/logans-first-halloween-costume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/11/logans-first-halloween-costume/</guid>
      <description>Halloween has always been a big event in the Sullivan household, as anyone who knew my sisters and I in grade school could tell you. Every year, we each decided what we wanted to be, and my Mom and Dad worked together on the costumes–Mom found patterns and fabric and did the sewing, and Dad constructed the 3D parts of the costume, like all the masks, the nose and hat on the tin man, the muscles on the dinosaur.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>