<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bleach Shirts on Annie Sullivan</title>
    <link>/categories/bleach-shirts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bleach Shirts on Annie Sullivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/bleach-shirts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleach Shirts on the Glowforge</title>
      <link>/2018/12/bleach-shirts-on-the-glowforge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/bleach-shirts-on-the-glowforge/</guid>
      <description>I’ve made a bunch of bleach shirts using stencil vinyl/contact paper on my cricut. But I really wanted to try it on my Glowforge, since it can cut higher detail stencils. I also wanted to try switching to freezer paper, so that I can iron/heat gun the bleached areas of the shirt to make them lighter.
The big problem I had with freezer paper (on both the cricut and the Glowforge) is that it curls up a ton, and I didn’t have a good way to transfer the stencil to the shirt, especially stencils with multiple tiny bits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleach Shirts with Polyester Blends</title>
      <link>/2018/11/bleach-shirts-with-polyester-blends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/11/bleach-shirts-with-polyester-blends/</guid>
      <description>All the tutorials for making bleach shirts say to use 100% cotton. But I had some Old Navy 60% cotton 40% polyester blend shirts sitting around, and the kids need some long sleeve shirts for winter. They’ve been asking about deathly hallows shirts after seeing someone wearing one, so I decided to give it a shot.
I made stencils using contact paper on the Cricut. One problem I’ve had is that it’s super easy to make stencils with vinyl or contact paper, but then you can’t iron to lighten the bleach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making bleach shirts with stencils cut on Cricut Maker</title>
      <link>/2018/06/bleach-shirts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/bleach-shirts/</guid>
      <description>The Basics I randomly happened upon this subreddit full of bleach shirt pictures and was totally mesmerized. So many different possibilities, and such a simple process. So I started reading up. There are a lot of variations in the process, but making bleach shirts mostly looks like this:
 Use a 100% cotton shirt. Wash the shirt. Lots of shirts come with chemicals on them that will stop the bleach from working.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>