<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2012s on Annie Sullivan</title>
    <link>/2012/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2012s on Annie Sullivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Printed Metal Christmas Ornaments: Biodh Duil</title>
      <link>/2012/12/biodh-duil-ornaments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/12/biodh-duil-ornaments/</guid>
      <description>My uncle Dick passed away this year, and it was a very sad time for our family because he was such an amazing person and we will all miss him so much. For Christmas, I wanted to do something to remember him. He always loved gadgets and new technology, so I decided to design gifts in Tinkercad and have them 3D printed for the family.
When our family was going through some hard times, Uncle Dick and his daughter Colleen got together and designed a family logo, a tree with a heart and the words “Biodh Duil” (Irish imperative form of the verb “hope”) written below it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitten Christmas Tree Skirt Made with Silhouette Cameo</title>
      <link>/2012/11/christmas-tree-skirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/11/christmas-tree-skirt/</guid>
      <description>I just got a Silhouette Cameo and I am really excited to use it! It can cut paper, cardstock, fabric, vinyl, stickers, and even temporary tattoos into whatever shapes you can put into vector graphic format on your computer. After a few experiments with cardstock, I wanted to make something real. I decided to start small, with a Christmas tree skirt.
I had seen some photos of a tree skirt with mittens on it, and since we live in the mitten state now I thought it would be fun do do something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logan&#39;s First Halloween Costume: Max&#39;s Wolfsuit from Where the Wild Things Are</title>
      <link>/2012/11/logans-first-halloween-costume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/11/logans-first-halloween-costume/</guid>
      <description>Halloween has always been a big event in the Sullivan household, as anyone who knew my sisters and I in grade school could tell you. Every year, we each decided what we wanted to be, and my Mom and Dad worked together on the costumes–Mom found patterns and fabric and did the sewing, and Dad constructed the 3D parts of the costume, like all the masks, the nose and hat on the tin man, the muscles on the dinosaur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Up Themed Nursery Decoupage</title>
      <link>/2012/10/up-themed-nursery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/10/up-themed-nursery/</guid>
      <description>I don’t usually do movie-themed home decor, but when we moved into our new house and I was thinking about Logan’s room, “Adventure is Out There!” really stuck with me. Logan has been walking for two months and he climbs anything he can, goes down the slide by himself, runs after cats and squirrels, and generally finds adventure at every turn. And I really liked the art from the movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knitting a Red Wings Hockey Jersey</title>
      <link>/2012/09/knitting-a-red-wings-hockey-jersey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/09/knitting-a-red-wings-hockey-jersey/</guid>
      <description>My grandmother taught me to knit when I was 8 or 9 years old, and I’ve been doing knitting projects on and off ever since. I switch back and forth between making things from patterns and designing them myself. I don’t really know what I’m doing; I make things up as I go and look up techniques in my trusty copy of Stitch ‘n Bitch if I get lost. Several years ago, I made my husband Doug a sweater, but he doesn’t wear it much because it needs to be hand-washed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First 3D printing project: Ladybug!</title>
      <link>/2012/03/first-3d-printing-project-ladybug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/03/first-3d-printing-project-ladybug/</guid>
      <description>My friend Kai started this amazing company called Tinkercad–you can design 3D models online and then print them out either using a 3D printing service or with a MakerBot. I wanted to try it out, so I decided to start with a ladybug. Tinkercad is a solid modeling tool, so I used squashed spheres to make the ladybug–a little one for the head, a bigger one for the body, and a bigger one split in half for the wings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>