<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Metal Etching on Annie Sullivan</title>
    <link>/categories/metal-etching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Metal Etching on Annie Sullivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/metal-etching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Metal Etching with the Glowforge</title>
      <link>/2019/02/metal-etching-with-glowforge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/02/metal-etching-with-glowforge/</guid>
      <description>Warning
Metal etching can be dangerous! If you&amp;rsquo;re going to try this, make sure to read all red the warning text at the bottom of the Edinburgh Etch page first!
Also note that copper is reflective. Laser forum users warn that there’s a risk of the beam bouncing off the copper and back into the laser head. I scuffed the copper prior to lasering to avoid this, but I&amp;rsquo;m not certain how big of a risk this is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Etching Photos onto Metal</title>
      <link>/2017/12/etching-photos-on-metal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/etching-photos-on-metal/</guid>
      <description>Warning
Metal etching can be dangerous! If you&amp;rsquo;re going to try this, make sure to read all red the warning text at the bottom of the Edinburgh Etch page first!  The big reason I spent all the effort learning to use press n peel paper to etch (instead of cutting vinyl stencils on my cameo) is that I really wanted to be able to get the fine detail needed to etch a photograph onto metal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to etch metal: Edinburgh etch on copper and brass stamping blanks</title>
      <link>/2017/12/learning-to-etch-metal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/learning-to-etch-metal/</guid>
      <description>Warning
Metal etching can be dangerous! If you&amp;rsquo;re going to try this, make sure to read all red the warning text at the bottom of the Edinburgh Etch page first!  When I took the laser cutter class at Maker Works and learned about all the different materials you can etch, I was really interested in learning how to etch metal. But most lasers at makerspaces and such are CO2 lasers, which can’t etch metal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>