<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2013s on Annie Sullivan</title>
    <link>/2013/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2013s on Annie Sullivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Etched Glass Ornaments</title>
      <link>/2013/12/laser-etched-glass-ornaments/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/12/laser-etched-glass-ornaments/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been having a lot of trouble getting photos to look good on ornaments, so I decided to try something else. I had a really cute set of Logan’s footprints from the hospital, and I scanned it in. I wanted to figure out the best way to convert the image to a black and white bitmap, so I could experiment to see which method would etch best on glass. I tried a few different methods:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween 2013: Sewing a Curious George Costume</title>
      <link>/2013/10/halloween-2013-curious-george/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/10/halloween-2013-curious-george/</guid>
      <description>This Halloween, Logan was obsessed with Curious George. So it was easy to pick out a costume idea for him. I picked up some brown fleece and sewed up the same Running With Scissors pattern I used last year. Here’s a pic of Logan trying it on (sorry for the blurriness, he’s pretty hard to catch standing still!)
  Jumping on the bed wearing the costume base. Could only get a blurry picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Etched Corian Marvel Coasters</title>
      <link>/2013/10/laser-etched-corian-coasters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/10/laser-etched-corian-coasters/</guid>
      <description>At one point, we were considering remodeling our kitchen, and we got some Corian samples. We didn’t end up doing the remodel, but we left them sitting around the house to see how durable they are. My brother-in-law had always thought they made cool coasters.
When I took the laser class at Maker Works, I noticed one of the materials that can be etched is Corian. Since my brother-in-law loves superheroes, I thought superhero coasters would be a cool Christmas present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter Shirt with Stencil Vinyl and Fabric Paint</title>
      <link>/2013/10/harry-potter-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/10/harry-potter-shirt/</guid>
      <description>I happened upon the Harry P font and decided it would be fun to make a quick shirt for Logan. I typed in some text and drew some footprints in Silhouette Studio, and then printed onto stencil vinyl on my cameo. I used a sponge to paint through the stencil, fading away the footprints.
  
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Using the Laser: Etched Wood Photo Ornaments</title>
      <link>/2013/10/first-time-using-the-laser/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/10/first-time-using-the-laser/</guid>
      <description>I got really excited after taking the laser class at Maker Works and decided to try a simple project to start. I didn’t want to worry about dithering photos, so I ran a batch job on all our family photos, putting them through Vector Magic to see which ones converted to single-color vectors the best.
I picked a few of the best ones, added some text in illustrator, and made cut lines for ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>