<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leather on Annie Sullivan</title>
    <link>/categories/leather/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Leather on Annie Sullivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/leather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Middle Earth Field Notes Cover</title>
      <link>/2018/08/middle-earth-leather-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/middle-earth-leather-journal/</guid>
      <description>I saw these beautiful map journals and thought it would be fun to make one with a fictional map. Doug’s birthday was coming up and he loves Lord of the Rings, so I decided to try making a Field Notes cover that’s a map of middle earth. I started with the template I used for the Marauder’s Map Field Notes Cover. While I was making the Calvin and Hobbes journal, I made some other journal templates, including a Field Notes cover with pen loop:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calvin  Hobbes Moleskine Cover</title>
      <link>/2018/08/calvin-hobbes-moleskine-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/calvin-hobbes-moleskine-cover/</guid>
      <description>I had a lot of fun making the Marauder’s Map Fields Notes Cover, and I wanted to try something just a little bit more complex. Plus I needed a cover for a bigger journal. So I decided to extend the field notes cover in Illustrator to fit a 5″x8.25″ Moleskine Cahier Journal, and add a pen loop and snap.
Here’s a link to my design, in case anyone wants to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leather field notes cover</title>
      <link>/2018/08/leather-field-notes-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/08/leather-field-notes-cover/</guid>
      <description>I really wanted to learn more about working with leather after making the Marauder’s Map bookmarks. So when I saw this field notes template on instructables I decided to extend the same design to a Field Notes cover.
I knew I wanted to dye the leather, and I’d need to be able to stitch together pieces, but I had no idea where to start beyond that. I’d heard great things about the customer service at Tandy Leather, so I headed down to the store with a ton of questions, and picked up some 2-3oz veg-tan leather,gel antique, waxed thread, stitching needles, and edge kote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Glowforge Project: Harry Potter Bookmarks</title>
      <link>/2018/07/first-glowforge-project-harry-potter-bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/first-glowforge-project-harry-potter-bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>I just got a Glowforge and I’m so excited! I haven’t had time to make much yet, but it came with a sample of leather, and I thought it would be fun to do Harry Potter bookmarks. So I found an image of the Marauder’s Map online, and quickly threw together the “I solemnly swear..” quote with footprints in Illustrator. I saved them as .png images and uploaded into the Glowforge app.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>