<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cricut/Silhouette on Annie Sullivan</title>
    <link>/categories/cricut/silhouette/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cricut/Silhouette on Annie Sullivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/cricut/silhouette/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleach Shirts with Polyester Blends</title>
      <link>/2018/11/bleach-shirts-with-polyester-blends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/11/bleach-shirts-with-polyester-blends/</guid>
      <description>All the tutorials for making bleach shirts say to use 100% cotton. But I had some Old Navy 60% cotton 40% polyester blend shirts sitting around, and the kids need some long sleeve shirts for winter. They’ve been asking about deathly hallows shirts after seeing someone wearing one, so I decided to give it a shot.
I made stencils using contact paper on the Cricut. One problem I’ve had is that it’s super easy to make stencils with vinyl or contact paper, but then you can’t iron to lighten the bleach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making bleach shirts with stencils cut on Cricut Maker</title>
      <link>/2018/06/bleach-shirts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/bleach-shirts/</guid>
      <description>The Basics I randomly happened upon this subreddit full of bleach shirt pictures and was totally mesmerized. So many different possibilities, and such a simple process. So I started reading up. There are a lot of variations in the process, but making bleach shirts mostly looks like this:
 Use a 100% cotton shirt. Wash the shirt. Lots of shirts come with chemicals on them that will stop the bleach from working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Porcelain Pen Ceramic Mug</title>
      <link>/2018/05/decorating-mugs-with-porcelain-pen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/decorating-mugs-with-porcelain-pen/</guid>
      <description>Even after twenty years as a woman in tech, this article about One Direction fans and especially the Larries brought a fresh perspective. I mentioned it to my sister, and as usual, she was way ahead of me. She also loves coffee, so when I found out about porcelain pens, I thought it would be cool to try and make her a Larry Stylinson mug.
I did a Google image search for a good picture and decided to start with this one:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandblasting Pint Glasses and Stemless Wine Glasses</title>
      <link>/2018/04/sandblasting-glass/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/sandblasting-glass/</guid>
      <description>We have been running out of glasses lately and I’ve been thinking about decorating my own. I’ve seen some cool pictures of frosted glass online and wanted to try something like that myself. The first thing I tried was etching cream, which is pretty cheap and easy to find, but I ran into some big problems.
  You can see where the etching cream leaked at the top of the glass, and where it dripped around the back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter Shirt with Stencil Vinyl and Fabric Paint</title>
      <link>/2013/10/harry-potter-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2013/10/harry-potter-shirt/</guid>
      <description>I happened upon the Harry P font and decided it would be fun to make a quick shirt for Logan. I typed in some text and drew some footprints in Silhouette Studio, and then printed onto stencil vinyl on my cameo. I used a sponge to paint through the stencil, fading away the footprints.
  
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitten Christmas Tree Skirt Made with Silhouette Cameo</title>
      <link>/2012/11/christmas-tree-skirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2012/11/christmas-tree-skirt/</guid>
      <description>I just got a Silhouette Cameo and I am really excited to use it! It can cut paper, cardstock, fabric, vinyl, stickers, and even temporary tattoos into whatever shapes you can put into vector graphic format on your computer. After a few experiments with cardstock, I wanted to make something real. I decided to start small, with a Christmas tree skirt.
I had seen some photos of a tree skirt with mittens on it, and since we live in the mitten state now I thought it would be fun do do something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>